The Wild, Wild West just got wilder with Tom and Jerry on the ranch!
Tom and Jerry Cowboy Up! is a animation, comedy, family
film directed by Darrell Van Citters.
This time, the rivals team up to help a cowgirl and her brother save their
homestead from a greedy land-grabber, and they’re going to need some help!
Jerry’s three precocious nephews are all ready for action, and
Tom is rounding up a posse of prairie dogs.
But can a ragtag band of varmints defeat a deceitful desperado
determined to deceive a damsel in distress?
No matter what happens with Tom and Jerry in the saddle,
it’ll be a rootin’ tootin’ good time!
The Marshal (voice), played by George Ackles.
Bumpy (voice), played by Sean Burgos.
Duke (voice), played by Trevor Devall.
August Critchley (voice), played by Chris Edgerly.
Scruffy (voice), played by Georgie Kidder.
Bentley (voice), played by Justin Michael.
Tom and Jerry: Cowboy Up!
is a 2022 American animated direct-to-video Western comedy film
starring Tom and Jerry, produced by Warner Bros.
It is the first Tom and Jerry direct-to-video animated film in five years since 2017's Tom and
Jerry: Willy Wonka and the Chocolate Factory, and a continuation of the film series.
It is also the first Tom and Jerry direct-to-video animated film to feature the animation services of Renegade Animation, the studio
that animated The Tom and Jerry Show (2014–21) and Tom and Jerry in New York (2021), and Slap Happy Cartoons in Canada.
It was released to DVD and digital in the United
States and Canada on January 25, 2022.
An animated Christmas film called Tom and Jerry: Snowman's Land
was released later that year in November 2022.
The tone is lighthearted.